KEVIN BAUGUS

1539 Highfield CT, NLV, NV, 89032

Kbaugus31@gmail.com 702-743-2134

OBJECTIVE

Upbeat and flexible customer service minded individual. I am seeking a Sales Manager/ sales representative position.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

I have 8 years of customer service and 4 years as a sales manager. As a sales associate who is goal-oriented and consistently seeking opportunities for growth with a company and increasing training knowledge. I have exceeded every job that I have had. I am a team player that likes to help others. I am looking for a long term with a company like this one so I can grow and help the company grow as well.

EXPERIENCE

Cox Communication Las Vegas NV

06/18 to 03/20

Third Party sales/ Walmart

As a third-party sales rep I take care of the customer's needs and not just Cox services for anything that is needed in the store. My time with cox I have become an ambassador for the team. Going to different stores helping as needed with the training of others I have been at 200% to goal on revenue and psu. I have won the dash and am going to be a rising star.

Wyndham Vacation, Las Vegas NV Inbound calls sales/ customer service

03/18 to 06/18

As an inbound sales rep I made sure the customer got the best deal that we had and if anything was wrong, I made sure that I could fix it for them so we could retain the customer.

Phoenix Branding Inc. Phoenix AZ Manager/CEO/ Owner

02/17 to 03/18

Third party sales in Costco

- As a manager I was responsible for interviews, training, running impact's and team building and going to the field and leading from the front. Work with Global Directors or Customer Engagement Program Managers to execute the lead generation marketing campaigns
- Work with product marketing to develop and promote customer success stories
- Create, execute, and optimize direct-to-consumer marketing plans to ensure traffic goals are met for promotional.

Maven Marketing, Las Vegas NV

Assistant Manager/Account Manager

03/15 to 02/17

 As an Account Manager I was responsible for training in the office and in the field, I also learned how to build a team and maintain my sales. As an Assistant Manager I learned how to do payroll, scheduling and how to run an office. Direct Marketing Specialists apply knowledge of business objectives, marketing strategy, customers, distribution channels and the market to develop and produce direct response. Multi-channel marketing campaigns and collateral Channels such as print, digital and face to face to sell our products to consumers.

Smith's Food and Drug Las Vegas NV

02/11 to 3/15

I communicated with upper managers with all the sales to and merchandise needs. Made sure all the store inventory numbers were right. made sure that the customer had what they needed.

Running

forklifts.

Managing the receipt, storage and outflow of products or materials managing these functions for multiple departments.

With Smarts can you can improve productivity, accuracy, and visibility across your warehouse and manage the influx and outflow of goods and materials throughout the entire inventory management life cycle.

Receive Inventory Process Orders Pick, Pack and Ship Process Returns

Based on industry best practices for both company and omnichannel fulfillment, Smart Scan dynamically delivers data to operators so they can seamlessly react to changing priorities and measure warehouse performance in real-time, enabling your 3PL to optimize labor efficiency and achieve 100% order and profit and loss.

Truck Driver.

2/2006 to 03/2013 Las Vegas Paving

Completed a daily pre-trip inspection checklist before first delivery of the day. Selected the most efficient routes in compliance with delivery instructions and fuel policy. Picked up and delivered cargo in a tractor-trailer using knowledge of roads, highways and interstates. Checked vehicle's fluid levels and tire pressure and scheduled any required repairs. Operated motor vehicles in a safe and efficient manner. Verified loads against shipping papers. I also ran 1080 frontend loaders, skid-steer loaders

Truck Driver

4/2000 to 02/2006 Southern Nevada Paving

Completed a daily pre-trip inspection checklist before first delivery of the day. Selected the most efficient routes in compliance with delivery instructions and fuel policy. Picked up and delivered cargo in a tractor-trailer using knowledge of roads, highways and interstates. Checked vehicle\'s fluid levels and tire pressure and scheduled any required repairs. Operated motor vehicles in a safe and efficient manner. Verified loads against shipping papers I also ran 1080 frontend loaders, skid-steer loaders

Truck Driver / Pitcher

3/1998 to 03/2000 Republic Services

Completed a daily pre-trip inspection checklist before first delivery of the day. Selected the most efficient routes in compliance with delivery instructions and fuel policy. Picked up and delivered cargo in a tractor-trailer using knowledge of roads, highways and interstates. Checked vehicle\\'s fluid levels and tire pressure and scheduled any required repairs.

Operated motor vehicles in a safe and efficient manner. Verified loads against shipping papers.

EDUCATION Rancho High School

1983/1987

COMPUTER SKILLS

Java, Visual Basic, MS Excel, Word, PowerPoint MS Access, MySQL, Oracle AutoCAD, SolidWorks MATLAB, Mathematica Windows, Linux, Mac OS